<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Blues Primer</string>
    <string name="hint">hint</string>
    <string name="TryCommand">TryCommand</string>
    <string name="ToggleButton">ToggleButton</string>
    <string name="invalid">invalid</string>
    <string name="about">The objective of A Minor Blues Primer is to get you rocking some Blues guitar solos with a bare minimum of effort. First we\'ll start with a basic lesson on Blues music theory, then we\'ll move forward to a step by step audio and video tutorial showing you a few awesome solos that will take you gently through a standard 12 bar Blues chord progression. Once you are comfortable with the supplied solos, you may review tips and tricks on how to build your own custom riffs and set yourself free to explore your own creative voice in world of Blues guitar improvisation. This home school method worked for me, and it will work for you too!</string>
    <string name="twelvebarblues">The following is a standard A minor blues chord progression in music notation. Each bar represents 4 beats for a total of 12 bars in a repeating pattern.</string>
    <string name="barchords">The three basic bar chords below are all you will need to get started in A minor blues rhythm guitar. Guitarists will augment these basic chords forms with other colour tones to keep things interesting. The first chord in the A minor blues progression is A minor with the root note at the fifth fret on the sixth string of the guitar neck. </string>
    <string name="scaleviewtext">The key to blues guitar improvisation is knowing which scale to play against any given chord in the 12 bar blues progression. There are five patterns in the blues scale. It is good practise to know these patterns thoroughly. An experienced blues soloist will be able to move his/her fingers with ease from one scale pattern to the next across the entire fretboard.</string>
    <string name="start">It is possible to play guitar by ear and feel, however, a little music theory knowledge will make the learning process that much easier. So take a moment to review our minimalist\'s guide to blues guitar. Here we provide just enough music theory to get the ball rolling. When you are ready, push forward with our tutorials in Blues guitar soloing. And don\'t forget to tune your guitar! </string>
    <string name="solo">Here we will teach you three awesome Blues solos note for note through a laid back 12 bar blues shuffle progression. Choose a skill level based on your knowledge and ability, then press go to begin. Press play to listen to the solo included in each lesson.</string>
    <string name="advbluesriff1of3">This riff covers the first four bars in our twelve bar blues progression. We will use the blues scale pattern #1 at the fifth fret for soloing over the A minor chord.</string>
    <string name="bluesolospractise">Congratulations! You have completed all 12 bars of the:</string>
    <string name="bluessolopractise1">Click the button below to play back the blues rhythm track included in this tutorial. This audio file will loop continuously until you press stop. Use this music for rhythm accompanyment as you practise soloing. Once you are comforable with the riffs included in the tutorials, go on to main menu and review tips and tricks for blues guitar improvisation.</string>
    <string name="improv">In Blues music, it is the scale pattern, blue note and 12 bar chord progression that are core to the sound in this musical genre. The following are few key concepts and techniques that will help clear the path to successful blues guitar improvistion:</string>
    <string name="conceptsandtechniques1">The five blues scale patterns are all connected and repeat as you move up and down the guitar neck. Keep an eye on the root note of the scale you are using while soloing. This will help you orient yourself as you solo through chord changes in twelve bar blues. Also, bare in mind that any riff built around a particular scale pattern can be transposed into any other key by simply shifting fret position.</string>
    <string name="conceptsandtechniques2">The following are a few things to consider when building your own riffs for soloing:</string>
    <string name="check_license">Check license</string>
    <string name="checking_license">Checking license...</string>
    <string name="dont_allow">Don\'t allow the user access</string>
    <string name="allow">Allow the user access</string>
    <string name="application_error">Application error: %1$s</string>
    <!-- Unlicensed dialog messages -->
    <string name="unlicensed_dialog_title">Application not licensed</string>
    <string name="unlicensed_dialog_body">This application is not licensed. Please purchase it from Android Market.</string>
    <string name="buy_button">Buy app</string>
    <string name="quit_button">Exit</string>

</resources>